It may not be a real illness but K-drama fever is sweeping Asia with as much force as an infectious disease.
这也许不是一种真正的疾病，但韩剧热正像传染病一样席卷亚洲。
The latest hit show to come out of South Korea has already claimed over 440 million victims in China alone, where it's being simulcast.
韩国最新热门电视剧仅在中国同步播出就已经吸引了超过4.4亿观众。
Many millions more are glued to their screens across the continent.
亚洲大陆还有数百万观众紧盯着屏幕。
'Descendants of the Sun' is the latest in a long line of TV dramas to come out of Korea which have taken Asia by storm.
《太阳的后裔》是韩国一系列风靡亚洲的电视剧中的最新一部。
The usual theme of star-crossed lovers is still very much there but there's a twist which many of its fans say gives this drama a distinctive flavour.
常见的命运多舛的恋人主题依然存在，但有一个转折，许多粉丝说这个转折让这部剧有了独特的风味。
It's a military romance which is set in a fictional European country.
这是一部以一个虚构的欧洲国家为背景的军队爱情剧。
Ms Gao from Beijing said, "The military theme does not usually appear frequently in TV shows so combined with the romantic theme, this is not like other Korean soap operas."
来自北京的高女士说：“军事主题在电视剧中通常不常出现，所以和爱情主题相结合后，这部剧和其他韩国肥皂剧不一样。”
The female lead, played by Song Hye-kyo, is a surgeon, while her male counterpart, played by Song Joong-ki, is a special forces captain.
由宋慧乔饰演的女主角是一名外科医生，而由宋仲基饰演的男主角是一名特种部队队长。
"Unlike most Korean dramas which are about a rich guy who falls in love with a poor, golden-hearted girl, the story feels more like the love story of two evenly-matched adults," says Chen Yuanni, from Beijing.
来自北京的陈媛妮说：“与大多数韩国电视剧中富家子弟爱上贫穷但心地善良的女孩的情节不同，这个故事感觉更像是两个旗鼓相当的成年人之间的爱情故事。”
But it's not just Asia which has seen a boom in the popularity of foreign-language TV dramas in recent years.
但近年来，并非只有亚洲出现了外语电视剧热度激增的情况。
Since the Danish crime drama, The Killing, was first aired on the BBC in 2011, the nation has been gripped by so-called Nordic Noir.
自2011年丹麦犯罪剧《谋杀》在英国广播公司首播以来，所谓的北欧黑色电影就吸引了这个国家（英国）的观众。
What surprises some is that it's not only thrillers, such as The Bridge, which have captured the imagination of British viewers.
令一些人惊讶的是，不只是像《桥》这样的惊悚片吸引了英国观众的想象力。
There have also been ratings successes for shows such as Borgen - about coalition politics - and 1864 - a drama about an obscure 19th century war between Denmark and Prussia.
像关于联合政治的《权力的堡垒》和关于19世纪丹麦与普鲁士之间一场鲜为人知的战争的《1864》等剧集在收视率上也取得了成功。
So why do these international dramas appeal when the cultural references are so remote from the experience of the viewers?
那么，当文化背景与观众的经历相差甚远时，这些国际电视剧为什么会有吸引力呢？
Perhaps the answer lies in this piece of advice for aspiring scriptwriters from the BBC's Writersroom: "Engaging characters are at the heart of all good drama, no matter how mainstream or unusual your idea may be."
也许答案就存在于英国广播公司编剧室给有抱负的编剧的这条建议中：“吸引人的角色是所有优秀电视剧的核心，无论你的想法多么主流或多么与众不同。”
So if the characters are strong enough, it doesn't matter if they're from Sichuan, Seoul or Sweden.
所以，如果角色足够有吸引力，他们来自四川、首尔还是瑞典都没关系。